Register of the John Davis Lodge papers, 1886-1987
Hoover Institution Archives
- Ambassador to Switzerland (1983-1985) File, 1982-1987 (Boxes 259-280)
  - Correspondence, 1982-1987
    - Damio, Mr. and Mrs. Roger, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 269: 46)
    - Davis, Glenn, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 269: 47)
    - Davis, Nathaniel, 1983 (Box-folder 269: 48)
    - Davis, Shelby Cullom, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 269: 49)
    - DeBearn, Gaston, 1983 (Box-folder 270: 1)
    - DeForest, Jack, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 270: 2)
    - DeLong, Thomas, 1987 (Box-folder 270: 3)
    - Dempsey, John (Jack), 1984-1985 (Box-folder 270: 4)
    - DeNardis, Lawrence, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 270: 5)
    - Deukmejian, George, 1984 (Box-folder 270: 6)
    - Deutermann, Vice Admiral H. T., 1983 (Box-folder 270: 7)
    - Dewart, Thomas, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 270: 8)
    - Dickinson, William, 1984 (Box-folder 270: 9)
    - Dietrich, Marlene, 1983 (Box-folder 270: 10)
    - Dietrich, Paul, 1984 (Box-folder 270: 11)
    - Dohanas, Mr. and Mrs. Steven, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 270: 12)
    - Dole, Robert, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 270: 13)
    - Donovan, Stanley, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 270: 14)
    - Dudley, Henry, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 270: 15)
    - Dugan, Jonathan, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 270: 16)
    - Dugstad, Richard, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 270: 17)
    - Duke, Angier Biddle, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 270: 18)
    - Duran Quintero, Argelino, 1983 (Box-folder 270: 19)
    - Egan, John J., 1984 (Box-folder 270: 20)
    - Ellinger, John, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 270: 21)
    - Enders, Thomas, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 270: 22)
    - Eppes, William D., 1983-1985 (Box-folder 270: 23)
    - Erize, Jeannette de, 1983 (Box-folder 270: 24)
    - Etting, Mr. and Mrs. Emlen, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 270: 25)
    - Evans, Thomas W., 1983 (Box-folder 270: 26)
    - Feisal, Alfred, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 270: 27)
    - Ferringa, Janine, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 270: 28)
    - Feuillatte, Nicolas, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 270: 29)
    - Field, David J., 1983 (Box-folder 270: 30)
    - Filosa, Gary, II, 1983 (Box-folder 270: 31)
    - Finger, Allen, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 270: 32)
    - Ford, George, 1983 (Box-folder 270: 33)
    - Fraleigh, William, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 270: 34)
    - Francoeur, Philip, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 270: 35)
    - Frelinghuysen, George, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 270: 36)
    - Frelinghuysen, Rodney, 1984 (Box-folder 270: 37)
    - Friedman, Irwin, 1984 (Box-folder 270: 38)
    - Friends of the Conservative Party, 1985 (Box-folder 270: 39)
    - Furgler, Kurt, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 270: 40)
    - Fynje de Salverda, Christian, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 270: 41)
    - Galbraith, Evan, 1984 (Box-folder 271: 1)
    - Gamble, William, 1984 (Box-folder 271: 2)
    - Gardner, Frederick, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 271: 3)
    - Garrigues, Antonio, 1985 (Box-folder 271: 4)
    - Gelardin, Albert, 1984 (Box-folder 271: 5)
    - Gerety, Pierce, 1983 (Box-folder 271: 6)
    - Gilman, Lawrence, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 271: 7)
    - Gingles, Robert, 1983 (Box-folder 271: 8)
    - Graeber, George, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 271: 9)
    - Grandville, Jean de la, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 271: 10)
    - Gray, Robert, 1983 (Box-folder 271: 11)
    - Griswold, Richard, Jr., 1984 (Box-folder 271: 12)
    - Hamilton, Lady Douglas, 1983 (Box-folder 271: 13)
    - Harlow, Arthur Brooks, 1983 (Box-folder 271: 14)
    - Harrop, William, 1984 (Box-folder 271: 15)
    - Hartmann, Rudolf, 1984 (Box-folder 271: 16)
    - Hatfield, Mark, 1983 (Box-folder 271: 17)
    - Hawkins, Richard, 1984 (Box-folder 271: 18)
    - Hearst, William Randolph, Jr., 1985 (Box-folder 271: 19)
    - Helms, Jesse, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 271: 20)
    - Heuven, Martin van, 1984 (Box-folder 271: 21)
    - Hill, Mrs. Robert, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 271: 22)
    - Hillings, Patrick, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 271: 23)
    - Hilson, Edwin, 1983 (Box-folder 271: 24)
    - House, Charles, 1983 (Box-folder 271: 25)
    - Hunsicker, Quincy, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 271: 26)
    - Ireland, Louise, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 271: 27)
    - Iribarne, Manuel Fraga, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 271: 28)
    - Iseli, Claude, 1984 (Box-folder 271: 29)
    - Janis, Martin E., 1983-1985 (Box-folder 271: 30)
    - Jarrell, 1985 (Box-folder 271: 31)
    - Javits, Eric, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 271: 32)
    - Jefferson Educational Foundation, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 271: 33)
    - Johnson, George B., 1985 (Box-folder 271: 34)
    - Jolles, Paul, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 271: 35)
    - Jova, Joseph, 1984 (Box-folder 271: 36)
    - Juan Carlos, King of Spain and Sophia, Queen of Spain, 1983 (Box-folder 271: 37)
    - Judd, Walter, undated (Box-folder 271: 38)
    - Katzenstein, Juan Carlos, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 271: 39)
    - Kaufmann, Arthur, 1984 (Box-folder 271: 40)
    - Kemp, Jack, 1985 (Box-folder 271: 41)
    - Kennedy, Dana F., 1983 (Box-folder 271: 42)
    - Kintner, William, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 271: 43)
    - Kirkpatrick, Jeane, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 271: 44)
    - Kriendler, John, 1983 (Box-folder 271: 45)
    - Kreisler, Edward, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 271: 46)
    - Lamont, Mrs. Gordon, 1983 (Box-folder 271: 47)
    - Leigh, Mrs. Douglas, 1983 (Box-folder 271: 48)
    - Leone-Moats, Alice, 1984 (Box-folder 271: 49)
    - Levy, Herman, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 271: 50)
    - Lichine, Alexis, 1983 (Box-folder 271: 51)
    - Lodge, Frederick Ziegler, 1984 (Box-folder 271: 52)
    - Lodge, George Cabot, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 271: 53)
    - Lodge, Mr. and Mrs. Henry Cabot, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 271: 54)
    - Loomis, Pat, 1985 (Box-folder 271: 55)
    - Lopez Moya, Fernando, 1984 (Box-folder 271: 56)
    - Luce, Clare Boothe, 1984 (Box-folder 271: 57)
    - Lugar, Richard, 1984 (Box-folder 271: 58)
    - L"thy, Hans, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 271: 59)
    - MacArthur, Jean, 1984 (Box-folder 271: 60)
    - Macauley, Thurston, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 271: 61)
    - Macaya, Ignacio, undated (Box-folder 271: 62)
    - McFarlane, Robert, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 272: 1)
    - McIlhenny, Henry P., 1983 (Box-folder 272: 2)
    - McKeon, Daniel, 1983 (Box-folder 272: 3)
    - McKinney, Stewart, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 272: 4)
    - MacKinnon, George, 1983 (Box-folder 272: 5)
    - McLaughlin, Robert, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 272: 6)
    - Madariaga Giraldo, Jose Maria de, 1985 (Box-folder 272: 7)
    - Martin-Gamero, Adolfo, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 272: 8)
    - Martin y Alonso-Martinez, Enrique, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 272: 9)
    - Marcus, Lily (Lodge), 1983-1985 (Box-folder 272: 10)
    - Mason, Anne, 1983 (Box-folder 272: 11)
    - Meese, Edwin, III, 1984 (Box-folder 272: 12)
    - Melady, Thomas, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 272: 13)
    - Menuhin, Yehudi, 1983 (Box-folder 272: 14)
    - Meskill, Thomas, 1984 (Box-folder 272: 15)
    - Mestre, Gore, 1983 (Box-folder 272: 16)
    - Mexican Academy of International Law, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 272: 17)
    - Michael, King of Rumania, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 272: 18)
    - Michel, Robert, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 272: 19)
    - Middendorf, William, II, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 272: 20)
    - Miles, Leland, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 272: 21)
    - Miller, William J., 1984 (Box-folder 272: 22)
    - Misch, Robert, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 272: 23)
    - Moore, Robin, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 272: 24)
    - Morris, Robert, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 272: 25)
    - Mosher, Robert, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 272: 26)
    - Mottu, Daniel, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 272: 27)
    - Muinos, 1985 (Box-folder 272: 28)
    - M"ller, Bernhard, 1984 (Box-folder 272: 29)
    - Muns, Alejandro de, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 272: 30)
    - Muralt, Alexander, 1983 (Box-folder 272: 31)
    - Muse, Martha, 1983 (Box-folder 272: 32)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1985 (Box-folder 273: 1)
    - National Review, 1984 (Box-folder 273: 2)
    - Nitze, Paul, 1983 (Box-folder 273: 3)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1985 (Box-folder 273: 4)
    - Norton, John, 1983 (Box-folder 273: 5)
    - Nunes, Frank, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 273: 6)
    - O'Brien, Edmund, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 273: 7)
    - O'Connor, George H., 1983-1985 (Box-folder 273: 8)
    - Olano, Luis de, 1983 (Box-folder 273: 9)
    - Oram, Frank, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 273: 10)
    - Ortiz, Frank, 1983 (Box-folder 273: 11)
    - Ortona, Egidio, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 273: 12)
    - Osborne, Kathleen, 1984 (Box-folder 273: 13)
    - Overton, Albert, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 273: 14)
    - Oyarzabal, Luis de, 1985 (Box-folder 273: 15)
    - Pabst, Robert, 1983 (Box-folder 273: 16)
    - Pasquaney Trust, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 273: 17)
    - Pell, John, 1983 (Box-folder 273: 18)
    - Pepper, Claude, 1984 (Box-folder 273: 19)
    - Percy, Charles, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 273: 20)
    - Pinies, Felix de, 1983 (Box-folder 273: 21)
    - Pollock, Howard, 1984 (Box-folder 273: 22)
    - Pourtales, Rudolf de, 1983 (Box-folder 273: 23)
    - Powell-Jones, John E., 1983-1985 (Box-folder 273: 24)
    - Quincy, Edmund, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 273: 25)
    - Quintana, Manolo, 1984 (Box-folder 273: 26)
    - Quintero, Argelino, 1985 (Box-folder 273: 27)
    - Rabb, Maxwell, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 273: 28)
    - Raymond, Allen, 1984 (Box-folder 273: 29)
    - Reagan, Nancy, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 273: 30)
    - Reagan, Ronald, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 273: 31)
    - Reed, Joseph V., 1983 (Box-folder 273: 32)
    - Reincke, Frederick, 1983 (Box-folder 273: 33)
    - Reynolds, Reginald, 1983 (Box-folder 273: 34)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham, 1984 (Box-folder 273: 35)
    - Riley, Richard, 1983 (Box-folder 273: 36)
    - Rimanoczy, Richard, 1985 (Box-folder 273: 37)
    - Robertson, Kenneth, 1983 (Box-folder 273: 38)
    - Roger, Philippe, 1984 (Box-folder 273: 39)
    - Rollins, Edward, 1984 (Box-folder 273: 40)
    - Roosevelt, Archibald, 1983 (Box-folder 273: 41)
    - Roots, John McCook, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 273: 42)
    - Sadruddin, Prince Aga Khan, 1985 (Box-folder 273: 43)
    - Sanford, Terry, 1984 (Box-folder 273: 44)
    - Sangiovanni, William, 1984 (Box-folder 273: 45)
    - Sans Mora, Miguel, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 274: 1)
    - Satrustegui, Javier de, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 274: 2)
    - Scheie, Harold, 1984 (Box-folder 274: 3)
    - Scheie, Polly, 1985 (Box-folder 274: 4)
    - Schlanger, Irving, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 274: 5)
    - Schmidtgen, Hans Joachim, 1984 (Box-folder 274: 6)
    - Sch"nburg, Count Rudi, 1983 (Box-folder 274: 7)
    - Sciclounoff, Pierre, 1984 (Box-folder 274: 8)
    - Sears, John, 1983 (Box-folder 274: 9)
    - Seelhofer, Hans, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 274: 10)
    - Seggerman, Harry, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 274: 11)
    - Shinn, Mr. and Mrs. James, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 274: 12)
    - Shultz, George, 1985 (Box-folder 274: 13)
    - Sill, Fred, 1985 (Box-folder 274: 14)
    - Simson, Veronica, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 274: 15)
    - Smedberg, Admiral William, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 274: 16)
    - Smith, Carleton, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 274: 17)
    - Smith, David, 1984 (Box-folder 274: 18)
    - Southworth, Hamilton, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 274: 19)
    - Sovereign Order of the Orthodox Knights Hospitaller of Saint John of Jerusalem, 1985 (Box-folder 274: 20)
    - Spain-U.S. Chamber of Commerce, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 274: 21)
    - Spanish Institute, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 274: 22-23)
    - Speaks, Charme, 1985 (Box-folder 274: 24)
    - Spiers, Ronald, 1984 (Box-folder 274: 25)
    - Stans, Maurice, 1985 (Box-folder 274: 26)
    - Stewart, Donald, 1984 (Box-folder 274: 27)
    - Stilson, Germaine, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 274: 28)
    - Stoelker, Charles, Jr., 1983 (Box-folder 274: 29)
    - Stolpen, Adam, 1983 (Box-folder 274: 30)
    - Stone, Roger J., Jr., 1983-1985 (Box-folder 274: 31-32)
    - Strausz-Hupe, Robert, 1984 (Box-folder 274: 33)
    - Streel, Helena de, 1984 (Box-folder 274: 34)
    - Supreme Court Historical Society, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 274: 35)
    - Swaebe, Geoffrey, 1983 (Box-folder 274: 36)
    - Tamayo-Gascue, Eduardo, 1983 (Box-folder 274: 37)
    - Tassie, Michael, 1985 (Box-folder 275: 1)
    - Taylor, Henry, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 275: 2)
    - Tharp, Thomas, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 275: 3)
    - Thaw, Lawrence, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 275: 4)
    - Thyssen-Bornemiszo, Hans Heinrich von, 1984 (Box-folder 275: 5)
    - Tournelle, Baronne de la, 1985 (Box-folder 275: 6)
    - Vurpillot, Jean-Phillipe, 1983 (Box-folder 275: 7)
    - Volpe, John, 1983 (Box-folder 275: 8)
    - Von Damm, Helene, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 275: 9)
    - Wadsworth, James, 1984 (Box-folder 275: 10)
    - Wallace, George C., 1984 (Box-folder 275: 11)
    - Walters, Vernon, 1985 (Box-folder 275: 12)
    - Webster, William, 1984 (Box-folder 275: 13)
    - Weicker, Lowell P., 1984 (Box-folder 275: 14)
    - Weinberger, Caspar, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 275: 15)
    - Weiss, Gaspard, 1983 (Box-folder 275: 16)
    - Welles, Benjamin, 1983 (Box-folder 275: 17)
    - Whittlesey, Faith, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 275: 18-19)
    - Wick, Charles, 1984 (Box-folder 275: 20)
    - Wilk, Willy, 1984 (Box-folder 275: 21)
    - Williams, J. Edgar, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 275: 22)
    - Williams, Paul, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 275: 23)
    - Williams, Robert, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 275: 24)
    - Wilson, Dalton, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 275: 25)
    - Wilson, Pete, 1984 (Box-folder 275: 26)
    - Wilson, Regina, 1983 (Box-folder 275: 27)
    - Wilson, William, 1983 (Box-folder 275: 28)
    - Women's National Republican Club, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 275: 29)
    - Woodbridge, Henry, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 275: 30)
    - Wright, Frank, 1983 (Box-folder 275: 31)
    - Zahedi, Ardeshir, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 275: 32)
    - Zehnder, Egon, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 275: 33)
    - Zutter, Mr. and Mrs. Philippe, 1985 (Box-folder 275: 34)
  - Office file, 1983-1985, undated
    - Chancery, building and dedication of (Box-folder 275: 35)
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 275: 36)
    - Memoranda (Box-folder 275: 37)
    - Procedures (Box-folder 275: 38)
    - Residence and representation expenses
      - 1983 (Box-folder 276: 1)
      - 1984 (Box-folder 276: 2)
      - 1985 (Box-folder 276: 3)
      - Outstanding bills (Box-folder 276: 4)
    - Security (Box-folder 276: 5)
    - Telegrams (Box-folder 276: 6)
    - Travel file
      - Cantonal calls (Box-folder 276: 7)
      - 1983
        - Barcelona (Box-folder 276: 8)
        - Malaga (Box-folder 276: 9)
        - United States (Box-folder 276: 10)
      - 1984
        - Spain (Box-folder 276: 11)
        - Washington D.C. (Box-folder 276: 12)
        - United States (Box-folder 276: 13)
        - Malaga (Box-folder 276: 14)
      - Travel vouchers (Box-folder 277: 1)
  - Speeches and writings, 1983-1985
    - Notes (Box-folder 277: 2)
    - Speeches, undated (Box-folder 277: 3)
    - 1983 (Box-folder 277: 4)
    - 1984 (Box-folder 277: 5-6)
    - 1985 (Box-folder 277: 7)
  - Subject file, 1983-1985, undated
    - American Security Council (Box-folder 277: 8)
    - Antartica (Box-folder 277: 9)
    - Argentina (Box-folder 277: 10)
    - Bolivar, Simon (Box-folder 277: 11)
    - Bretwalda Corporation (Box-folder 277: 12)
    - Brock, William, 1983 December 6 (Box-folder 277: 13)
      "Solving the International Economic Crisis--What We Must Do to Resist Protectionism," typescript.
    - Connecticut (Box-folder 277: 14)
    - Connecticut Nautilus Committee (Box-folder 277: 15)
    - Connecticut Republicans (Box-folder 277: 16)
    - Contadora (Box-folder 277: 17)
    - Council of the Americas (Box-folder 277: 18)
    - Diplomatic and Consular Officers, Retired (DACOR) (Box-folder 277: 19)
    - Election, 1984 (Box-folder 278: 1)
    - El Salvador (Box-folder 278: 2)
    - Falklands (Box-folder 278: 3)
    - Federation for American Immigration Reform (Box-folder 278: 4)
    - Former Members of Congress (Box-folder 278: 5)
    - Grenada (Box-folder 278: 6)
    - Hearst, William Randolph, Jr. (Box-folder 278: 7)
    - Heritage Foundation (Box-folder 278: 8)
    - Hofstra University (Box-folder 278: 9)
    - Hunger Relief (Box-folder 278: 10)
    - International Communication Agency (Box-folder 278: 11)
    - Jackson, Senator Henry (Box-folder 278: 12)
    - John Davis Lodge Center for International Studies (Box-folder 278: 13)
    - Kauffmann, Angelica (Box-folder 278: 14)
    - Kemp, Jack, 1985 February 2 (Box-folder 278: 15)
      "Agenda for a Global Entrepreneurial Era," typescript.
    - Kissinger, Henry (Box-folder 278: 16)
    - Middlesex School (Box-folder 278: 17)
    - Middendorf, J. William, II, 1984 February 8, undated (Box-folder 279: 1)
      "Nicaragua's Broken Promises - Five Years of Revolution Betrayed" and remarks for the Presidential classroom briefing, typescripts.
    - Miscellany (Box-folder 279: 2)
    - Morris, Robert (Box-folder 279: 3)
    - Namibia (Box-folder 279: 4)
    - National Press Club (Box-folder 279: 5)
    - National Review (Box-folder 279: 6)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box-folder 279: 7)
    - North Carolina - Committee on Inaugural Ceremonies (Box-folder 279: 8)
    - Perry, Commodore M. C. (Box-folder 279: 9)
    - Powell-Jones, John, 1984 November 15 (Box-folder 279: 10)
      "Stratford Canning En Suisse," typescript.
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 279: 11)
    - Republican National Committee/Reagan-Bush Campaign (Box-folder 279: 12)
    - Republicans Abroad (Box-folder 279: 13)
    - Rockford Institute (Box-folder 279: 14)
    - Space Technology Conference, Zurich, Switzerland, 1984 June 19-21 (Box-folder 279: 15)
    - Spain (Box-folder 279: 16)
    - Stevens Institute of Technology (Box-folder 279: 17)
    - Swiss-American Chamber of Commerce (Box-folder 279: 18)
    - Swiss-American Society, Bern (Box-folder 279: 19)
    - Thanksgiving, 1983 (Box-folder 279: 20)
    - Tinker Foundation (Box-folder 279: 21)
    - Trinity College (Box-folder 279: 22)
    - United Nations (Box-folder 279: 23)
    - United Services Organization (USO), 1983-1985 (Box-folder 280: 1-3)
    - United States Department of State (Box-folder 280: 4)
      Program statements.
    - Westport, Connecticut (Box-folder 280: 5)
    - Women's National Republican Club (Box-folder 280: 6)
    - Zimbabwe (Box-folder 280: 7)
- Declassified U.S. Government Records, 1947, 1950, 1953-1954 (Box 280)
  Formerly security-classified records of the U.S. government, released in full or in part. Includes some interfiled, unclassified government records. Arranged chronologically by date of release by Hoover, thereunder chronologically by date of creation.
  - 2011 October release of records, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 280: 8)
    Reports, cable, and chart relating to Spain.
  - 2015 November release of records, 1947, 1950 (Box-folder 280: 9)
    Includes Committee on Foreign Affairs memoranda ("Terms of Supplemental Appropriation for Relief Assistance to War Devastated Countries" and "Breaches of Contract and Good Faith by the United States Incident to and Since World War II") (1947); and a memorandum regarding, and drafts of, a resolution put forth by Lodge in the House of Representatives, referred by the Committee of Foreign Affairs, regarding Formosa (1950).
- Speech Cards, undated (Boxes 281-284)
  - Unsorted speech cards
- Scrapbooks, 1946-1961 (Boxes 285-311)
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1946 September 15 - 1946 October 28 (Box 285)
  - 1946 October 10 - 1946 November 6
  - 1946 October 27 - 1946 November 10
  - 1947 January-April (Box 286)
  - 1947 April-June
  - 1947 May-October (Box 287)
  - 1947 October - 1948 March
  - 1948 February-May (Box 288)
  - 1948 June-September
  - 1948 September - 1949 April (Box 289)
  - 1949 April-August (Box 290)
  - 1949 August - 1950 February (Box 291)
  - 1949 December - 1950 March
  - 1950 February-March (Box 292)
  - 1950 March-April
  - 1950 March-May
  - 1950 March-May (Box 293)
  - 1950 May-June
  - 1950 May-June (Box 294)
  - 1950 June
  - 1950 June-August (Box 295)
  - 1950 August-October
  - 1951 January (Box 296)
  - Souvenir photo album of Malaysia
  - Souvenir photo album of China
  - 1954-1955, Part 1 of 2, Page 1-200 (Box 297)
  - 1954-1955, Part 2 of 2, Page 201-359 (Box 298)
  - 1956, Part 1 of 3, Page 1-200 (Box 299)
  - 1956, Part 2 of 3, Page 201-400 (Box 300)
  - 1956, Part 3 of 3, Page 401-522 and covers (Box 301)
  - 1958, Part 1 of 2, Page 1-200 (Box 302)
  - 1958, Part 2 of 2, Page 201-304 and covers (Box 303)
  - 1959 (Box 304)
  - 1960, Part 1 of 2, Page 1-300 (Box 305)
  - 1960, Part 2 of 2, Page 301-586 and covers (Box 306)
  - 1961 (Box 307)
  - Miscellaneous newspapers and publications
  - Miscellaneous (Box 308)
  - CLOSED, 1957, 1959, 1961 (Boxes 310-311)
    Scrapbooks.
    Access
    Closed due to preservation concerns.
- Memorabilia, undated (Boxes 308-309)
- Sound Recordings, 1964-1984
  - Presentation of George Cabot Lodge's poetry to the Lincoln Library by John Davis Lodge, sound tape reel, 1970 December 1 (Tape cabinet)
  - Sound recording of John Davis Lodge speech "Spanish-American Friendship" to the American Club of Southern Spain, sound cassette, 1975
    Use copy reference number: 86005_a_0003650
    Leading up to the United States Bicentennial, John Davis Lodge discusses the historical circumstances leading to the development of a Spanish-American friendship and how freedom and a renewed sense of country stands in opposition to Communist encroachment.
  - Sound recording of John Davis Lodge's comments at the Conference for Moral Re-Armament, Switzerland, sound cassette, 1984 August 8
    Use copy reference number: 86005_a_0003657
  - Republican National Committee, "Go, Goldwater!," sound disc, 1964 (Record cabinet)
- Photographs, 1932-1985 (Photo file)
  Approximately 4442 prints / 7 albums / 121 envelopes.
  - 23 prints (Envelope A)
    Includes 1 print each of Gen. Michael Davison, Dr. Robert Strausz-Hupe, Jack Baird and Richard Nixon.
  - 9 prints of the USS St. Paul and the USS Northampton (Envelope B)
    Includes 1 print each of Vice-Adm. Charles Griffin and Vice-Adm. William Smedberg, III.
  - 52 negatives, unidentified (Envelope C)
  - 45 prints of unidentified landscapes and buildings (Envelope D-E)
  - 71 prints of unidentified people (Envelope F-G)
  - 30 prints (Envelope mH)
    Includes 5 prints of John D. Lodge as an actor; 2 prints of John D. Lodge and Edith Wharton; 1 print of the John D. Lodge family; 1 print of the Duke of Aosta; and 1 sheet of unidentified negatives.
  - 39 prints of John D. Lodge as a politician, 1946-1985 (Envelope I)
  - 68 prints of John D. Lodge as an actor, 1932-1942 (Envelope J-K)
  - 19 prints of Henry Cabot Lodge, Sr. at his summer home in Massachusetts (Envelope L)
  - 18 prints of Rear Admiral Charles Henry Davis (Envelope M)
  - 5 prints of John D. Lodge's grandchildren (Envelope N)
  - 23 prints of John D. Lodge's daughters, Lily and Beatrice (Envelope O)
  - 6 prints of the Lodge and Braggiotti families (Envelope P)
    Includes 1 print each of Mathilda Elizabeth Frelinghuysen Davis Lodge, Giles Lodge, and Countess Berthe de Pourtales.
  - 35 prints of Francesca Braggiotti Lodge (Envelope Q-R)
  - 2 prints of Mrs. George Cabot Lodge (Envelope S)
  - 2 prints of Henry Cabot Lodge, Jr. (Envelope T)
  - 5 prints of Villa Lodge (Envelope U)
  - 8 prints and 14 negatives (Envelope V)
    Includes 1 print of Villa Braggiotti in Florence, Italy; 1 print of post-World War II Poland; 1 print of Beatrice Lodge; and 4 negatives of Francesca Lodge.
  - 74 prints of Camp Pasquanay and Evan's School (Envelope W)
  - 14 prints portraying John D. Lodge during his U.S. Naval service, 1942-1946 (Envelope X)
  - 35 prints portraying John Davis Lodge during his congressional years, 1946-1950 (Envelope Y-Z)
    Includes 10 prints of the USS Tarawa; 4 prints of the 1946 campaign; and 6 prints of the Palermo Boys' Home.
  - 84 prints portraying John D. Lodge during his Governorship of Connecticut, 1950-1954 (Envelope AA-AD)